[Music]
[Música]
what's up you were here we had seen
qué pasa estabais aquí nos había visto
very good very good now closer the
muy buenas muy buenas ahora más cerca el
cable is not true that I have to change
cable no es verdad que tengo que cambiar
the tower as soon as possible as soon as possible we already
la torre cuanto antes cuanto antes ya
know what we should give away a
sabemos lo que debemos regalar un micro
new microphone no it's not the microphone dude in the [ __ ]
nuevo no no es el micro tío en la [__]
shitty tower in the [ __ ]
torre de [__] en la [__] torre de
shitty tower it doesn't make any sense gold
[__] no tiene ningún sentido de oro
what does it make no sense I mean
que hace no tiene ningún sentido o sea
the cable you move them and the microphone doesn't turn
el cable tú los mueves y el micro no se
off therefore the microphone difficult to
apaga por lo tanto el micro difícil
get power it's like it makes a
llegando corriente es como que hace un
cut that has to be something with the motherboard
corte eso tiene que ser cosa de la placa
or something in the tower sant like it can't be
o de algo de la torre sant en plan no
fixed I urgently need to change my PC
tiene arreglo tengo cambiar de pc
apart from home of course
urgentemente aparte de casa por supuesto
also well today we're going to watch a video
también bueno hoy vamos a ver un vídeo
from
de
turbo plan and yesterday he uploaded a video
turbo plan y es que ayer subió un vídeo
responding to Yuki's statement
respondiendo al comunicado de estar yuki
so let's see it you don't have to
así que vamos a verlo no hay que
listen to all the parts of course
escuchar todas las partes por supuesto
as long as what you are to the pse or
siempre y cuando lo que seas al pse o
welcome I mean I don't really like
bienvenido o sea no me hace mucha gracia
turbo black's hypocrisy and he doesn't say
la hipocresía de turbo black y no dice
I make a ten minute video in the
hago vídeo de diez minutos en la
description of his channel and now as if I
descripción de su canal y ahora como si
upload a 22 minute video well let's see what's
subo un vídeo de 22 bueno vamos a ver lo
up guys and girls welcome from
que tal chicos y chicas bienvenidos de
new to your channel favorites and
nuevo a vuestro canal favoritos y
origami reactions it turns out
reacciones de papiroflexia resulta ser
that following our last video
que a raíz de nuestro último vídeo
our last asked for criticism from the
nuestra última pidió crítica a la
youtuber streamer star yuki well it turns out
youtuber streamer star yuki pues resulta
that the subject has heated up and she has even
que se ha calentado el tema e incluso ha
responded that yuki is very very angry
respondido estar yuki muy muy enfadada
with this statement to which we are going to
con este comunicado al que vamos a
react now but given her visits
reaccionar ahora pero ante sus visitas a
so little to the [ __ ] of the tri turbo black
tan poquito al [__] del tri turbo black
I am going to put it in context for those who do not
voy a poner en contexto para los que no
know all the gold of this whole story
sepáis todo el oro de toda esta historia
with this look and I am going to give you a brief
con este look y os voy a hacer un breve
summary so that you understand it
resumen para que lo entendáis
perfectly it turns out that some time ago
perfectamente resulta que hace tiempo
six months or so I uploaded a
hace seis meses más o menos subí un
video talking about yuki a
vídeo hablando de estar yuki una
streamer who became very well known for
streamer que se hizo muy conocida por
reacting to videos of aurum plate
reaccionar a vídeos de aurum plate
ballet or lie it comes out literally she did not
ballet o mentira sale literalmente no se
become very well known for avid version of
hizo muy conocida por versión ávida de
agrón play we were seeing it in her
agrón play estuvimos viéndolo en su
statistics in her things and her
estadística en sus cosas y sus vídeos
most viewed videos were others okay hey would she
más vistos eran otros vale oye que
earn something for the videos that they
ganaría algo por lo de los vídeos que
uploaded on her secondary channel raseando
subían en su canal secundario raseando
well yes obviously but they were not her
pues sí evidentemente pero no eran sus
most viewed videos in eyes yes it is true
vídeos más vistos en ojos sí es cierto
that being here apart from having videos
de que estar aquí aparte de tener vídeos
reactions also has other videos
reacciones tiene también otros vídeos
playing games and doing other things
jugando a juegos y haciendo otras cosas
that no microphone does the
que no que micrófono tiene ahora el
turbo blah now
turbo bla
because it has it's like a little egg no what it
porque tiene es como un huevito no lo
has now is not like an egg
que tiene ahora no es como un huevito
there's a little kinder or rather reacting to
hay pequeño un kinder o sea reaccionar a
other people's videos I know that I know
vídeos de otras personas yo eso lo sé lo
perfectly well because there are a lot of
sé perfectamente porque hay muchísima
people who are coming to me to tell me no I
gente que me está viniendo a decir no
hope it's that you're lying because you're yuki
espero es que mientes porque estás yuki
no he doesn't upload that content and they demand
no no sube ese contenido y demandan
videos of yuki playing games and
vídeos de estar yuki jugando a juegos y
doing other types of things that are not
haciendo otro tipo de cosas que no sean
video reactions and I already know that he does
vídeo reacciones y yo ya lo sé que hace
other types of things but what caught my
otro tipo de cosas pero lo que me llamó
attention about djukic really what I
la atención de estar djukic en verdad lo
'm saying
que estoy diciendo
why is he taking so long with the air because he
porque está tardando con el aire porque
has a wool hat
tiene un gorro de lana
because he has a wool hat is the
porque tiene un gorro de lana es la
exaggerated amount of stolen videos that
exagerada cantidad de vídeos robados que
other youtubers have even though he
tiene otros youtubers a pesar de que
also has some other videos playing
también tenga algún otro vídeo jugando
some game doing some dancing even so
algún juego haciendo algún baile aún así
the percentage of reaction videos, let's say
el porcentaje de vídeos reacciones vamos
totally stolen and
de vídeos totalmente robados y sin
unedited videos is still huge I think that
editar sigue siendo enorme creo que
many of you are going to be surprised by the
muchos os vais a sorprender de la
amount of stolen videos he has
cantidad de vídeos robados que tiene
because it has surprised even me
porque es que me ha sorprendido hasta yo
what I'm going to tell you now is real
esto que os voy a decir ahora es real
then I'm going to  show more all the
luego os voy a mostrar más todas las
evidence of how I got to this
pruebas de cómo he llegado hasta esta
figure practically three quarters
cifra prácticamente tres cuartas partes
of the content that estar yuki has uploaded to
del contenido que ha subido estar yuki a
youtube or practically 75% of the
youtube o séase prácticamente un 75% del
content that estar yuki has uploaded is
contenido que ha subido estar yuki es
stolen content it's content it's video
contenido robado son contenidos es vídeo
reactions everything but but why does he have
reacciones todo pero pero porque tiene
that determination in a day after you keep me
ese empeño en un día tras you keep yo
because I kept my eye on it no
porque la echaba al ojo no vídeo
edited video reactions what you say well it's
reacciones editadas que dices bueno es
taken his work it's that he has summarized
que lleva su trabajo es que ha resumido
the video he has modified it he has
el vídeo le ha modificado le ha
commented on it no reaction video it's
comentado no vídeo reacción es
simply his face next to
simplemente su cara al lado de un vídeo
another person's video and uploaded without editing almost
de otra persona y subido sin editar casi
75% of its content so this is what
un 75% de su contenido entonces esto es
caught my attention and not
lo que a mí me llamó la atención y no
only that but he had a channel called
sólo eso sino que tenía un canal llamado
boom y arm and well and he supposedly still has it
boom y arm y bueno y lo sigue teniendo
with followers and
supuestamente con los seguidores y es
to this day he still says that the
que a día de hoy todavía pone que el
channel belongs to some followers and it's not
canal es de unos seguidores y no es
completely false the channel is his and it
completamente falso el canal es suyo y
's a channel that has a total of 40 million
es un canal que tiene total 40 millones
views and 100% of its videos or
de visitas y el 100% de sus vídeos o sea
270 videos that he has which are more videos
270 vídeos que tiene que son más vídeos
than his main channel has
de los que tienen su canal principal el
100% of the videos uploaded  this channel
100% de los vídeos subidos a este canal
are reaction videos and unedited
son vídeos reacciones y sin editar los
videos stolen literally one hundred
vídeos robados literalmente el cien por
percent from the channel and also well the video
cien del canal y además bueno las vídeo
rations are allowed
raciones están permitidas
and of course
y claro
amavet
amavet
let's take a look
vamos a echar un vistazo
bonnie armin let's see let's see
bonnie armin vamos a ver vamos a ver
what these vibes are like host
cómo son estas vibraciones [__]
300,000 subscribers eyes
300.000 suscriptores ojitos
in the last video
en el vídeo pasado lámparas
personalized lamps or
personalizadas o
very bad idea
muy mala idea
in the last video personalized or
en el vídeo pasado personalizada o
very bad idea the post that I have the
muy mala idea la publicación que tengo
most likes after a certain time I'm going to
más likes después de cierto tiempo voy a
order a lamp made of that and that
mandar a hacer una lámpara de eso y eso
was decorating my background in the
estaba decorando mi fondo en los
next
próximos vídeos
previous videos and I as a man of my word I'm going to the
anterior y yo como hombre de palabra voy
crux of my promise recapping a
al nudo de mi promesa recapitulando un
little I said that it was going to be a post
poco dije que iba a ser una publicación
where you guys were going to comment
donde ustedes iban a comentar
make a lamp the image that won
hacer una lámpara la imagen que ganó hoy
today like this is what he did is the boy on the
en día así ha hecho es el chico de la
bike of the rose of guadalupe les how do you
bici de la rosa de guadalupe les como
make a lamp like this dude it's simple
haces una lámpara de esto güey es simple
and there is the lamp my god
y ahí está la lámpara dios mío
look nothing more beautiful than this it's the
mira nada más hermoso que este es el
cost 400 values ​​like so us and in
costo 400 valores como así nosotros y en
me it steps on me video number 40 let's
mí me pisa vídeo número 40
see yes it's true we have to recognize
a ver sí que es verdad hay que reconocer
that what are the vibes the video
que lo que son las vibraciones el vídeo
and her of  every now and then he laughs and be
y ella de vez en cuando se ríe y sea
good okay you know but no no for the video it does
bueno vale sabe pero no no para el vídeo
n't contribute it's not going it's not going commenting on the
no aporta no va no va comentando lo
guys
chicos
[Music]
[Música]
what's up stream okay be to feel you
qué pasa stream vale sea para sentir lo
can do it I do
puede hacer
n't see it wrong with you doing it string you know
no lo veo mal que lo hagas string sabe
but since it's uploaded to youtube no no they are not they
pero ya que se suba a youtube no no son
are not legitimate use reactions
no son reacciones de uso legítimo
and I say this with all affection that things
y lo digo con todo cariño que las cosas
are we are
somos
watching the video we are
estamos viendo el vídeo lo estamos
watching the video of the guy h mass symphony
viendo el vídeo del tío h misa sinfonía
with her the corner
con ella la esquina
and
y
you can say let's see
tú puedes decir a ver
you can do it you can and it's not that my
tú puedes hacer tú puedes y no es que mi
fan asks me to upload it so that I
fan me piden que lo suba para que lo
upload it so that they know what they want your fan
suba para que sepa que quieren tu fan
done right
hecho
now I could take it and it's
yo ahora mismo podría [__] y
the video what they are watching here the
es el vídeo lo que están viendo aquí el
video
vídeo
faces to our channel are videos
caras a nuestro canal son vídeos
reactions totally but we are
reacciones totalmente pero estamos
commenting to in fact almost that the
comentando para de hecho casi que el
video what matters the least to me understand
vídeo lo que menos importa me entiende
if they give him permission in the problem and it will
si si le dan permiso en el problema y se
end and the subject ends in that in that he
acabará y se acaba el tema en que en que
predicted for example he does not care that he does it
auguró por ejemplo no le importa que lo
because the undo it okay but
haga porque la deshacerlo vale pero
man
hombre
upload it to youtube I
subirlo a youtube
don't know let's see let's see another
no sé yo a ver vamos a ver otra
legitimate use I already tell you that  it's not
uso legítimos ya os digo yo que no es
for example the memes the
para por ejemplo lo de los memes los
memes the
memes
others are not the same because
los de los demás no es lo mismo porque
the memes are a compilation of
los memes sí que es una recopilación de
memes you know the memes are not
memes sabe los memes no es
[Music]
[Música]
the memes are not the same because
lo de los memes no es lo mismo porque
the memes and that they are compilations and
los memes y que son recopilaciones y a
see how you react if you laugh
ver cómo reacciona si te ríes
this is not stolen content this
esto es no el contenido robado esto sí
is normal I mean in fact turbo plan
es normal o sea de hecho turbo plan
has a video reacting to memes it has
tiene vídeo reaccionando a memes tiene
a video related to the month it gives me the
un vídeo relacionado al mes me da la
bald and has nothing to say about
calvo y no tiene nada que decir lo de
the memes nothing
los memes nada
relationships story times
relaciones story times
[Music]
[Música]
they brought the April to put the sugar
trajeron lo abril para ponerle el azúcar
splenda stevia or whatever and where I
splenda stevia o lo que sea y donde no
'm not recording is that we can't do
estoy grabando es que no podemos hacer
the representation if this is clear the
la representación si esto está claro la
fault the smoothie to make coffee
culpa la licuado para hacer café a
often adores but it's not a friend it's
menudo adora pero no es un amigo es
floating we animal didn't bring miss
flotante nos animal no traía señorita
or rather like don't worry on
o sea así como que no te preocupes en
that day I bring you another message or that of
ese día te traigo otro mensaje o esa de
a complaint or rather chat is one can't
una denuncia o sea chat es uno no pueden
have the restaurants or rather that can't
tener los restaurantes o sea eso no
here they are commenting on story time
aquí están comentando a story time
but if I see that it is stopping it and is giving its
pero si veo que lo va parando y va
opinion  I'm not
opinando no
saying I could come get them I was
digo pudiera venir a buscarlos estaba
so happy he was safe well
tan feliz de que estuviera a salvo bueno
this could happen too from my point
éste podría pasar también desde mi punto
of view that could happen too
de vista ese podría pasar también
mas we've already said about me I don't care how
ms ya hemos dicho de mí me vale como
the Mexican forgets
olvida el mexicano
what we've said that is valid I mean
lo que hemos dicho que es válido o sea
this channel is not
este canal no es
100% stolen content
100% contenido robado
reacts to the most uncomfortable conversation
reacciona a la charla más incómoda a ver
let's see that
vamos a ver eso
[Music] right
[Música]
now eat a baby what I'm
ahora mismo comerme un bebé lo que estoy
saying is but of course damn I have to
diciendo es pero claro ostia me tengo
get used to this once it could still be a
que acostumbrar a esto una vez aún puede
coincidence
casualidad
[ __ ] like the thousand euro one according to the
[__] como la de mil euros según el
bank they have a thousand euros but it gives me [
banco tienen mil euros pero es a mí me
Music]
[Música]
a pique with the h he
un pique con el h
has
que tiene
and well it's a reaction that one we're going to
y bueno es una reacción esa esa la vamos
pass it to the stadium I would pass it
a pasar al estadio la pasaría
this was his viewing of visiting
este era su visionado de visita
and
i
my husband
mi marido
and and the food
y y la alimentación
and it's edited
y está editada
[Music]
[Música]
66 without reacting to video is allowed
66 sin reaccionar a vídeo está permitido
but of course
pero claro
I'm checking the channel a bit not to
estoy comprobando un poco el canal no a
see if it's like he had a plan they say they
ver si es como tuvo un plan dicen haber
stole content he doesn't see her content
robado contenido no ve el contenido de
she reacts thing yes it's
ella es ella reacciona cosa sí que es
true that there are reactions that are
verdad que hay reacciones que están
bordering on
rozando ahí él
fair use there I
el uso justo
agree with you dude the ideal would be
coincido contigo churra lo ideal sería
by  at least contribute an opinion or
por lo menos aportar una opinión o
criticism of the video card or devices just by
crítica del video card o aparatos de con
laughing at him for me the legitimate use is
solo reír a él para mí el uso legítimo
clear yes for me the legitimate use is
claro que sí para mí el uso legítimo es
that you stop the video and
que tú vayas parando el vídeo y vayas
comment on each thing your opinion that you
comentando cada cosa tu opinión que tú
contribute something that is when
aporte algo ahí es cuando está permitida
a video reaction is allowed
una vídeo reacción
some are a little sterile
algunas son un poquito estériles las
things things
cosas cosas
[Music]
[Música]
that had copinh
eso tenía copinh
n't put it mariñas that has
que no lo pongas mariñas que tiene
with me years
conmigo años
thanks side has hair
gracias lado tiene pelo
[Music]
[Música]
fernán's video was very strong the
el vídeo de fernán fue muy fuerte
video was very strong
el vídeo fue muy fuerte
[Music] he
[Música]
is a poet who is a poet
es un poeta que es un poeta
ah that
ah
's true I am a poet I am a poet
es cierto soy un poeta soy un poeta
that month
ese mes
and I singing my favorite song in
y yo cantando mi canción favorita en
English
inglés
the final video flower the cricket total
el vídeo final flor el cricket total
therefore and so basic that jokes laughter
por tanto y tan básico que bromea risa
of the songs of 20
de las canciones de 20
ah
ah
the note went away songs even because you
se fue la note canciones hasta porque te
like the track with pineapple
guste la pista con piña
well I
bueno
don't like
no me gusta
long live
vivas
now a woman throws a
ya ya una mujer tira una indirecta
loving hint to a man the brain of
amorosa a un hombre el cerebro del
man facua they mark each cow already beds
hombre facua marcan a cada vaca ya camas
[Music]
[Música]
I am a little delayed but I do not
estoy un poco [__] pero no le
hear him like a  song I'm
escucho como una canción
going to see the moment just because I know you
voy a ver el momento solo porque sé que
want to see it
queréis verlo
in fabric power
en tela poder
ah will
ah
sing with me since you want
cantará conmigo desde que tú quieres
me
a mí
first
primero
in
en
this
este
[Music]
[Música]
moment
momento
the moment of the moment
el momento del momento
what this drone is going to take out this
lo que va a sacar este drone esta
song backwards means the devil 666
canción al revés significa el [__] 666
in astrology I am illuminati angle
en astrología estoy ángulo illuminati
well it's already stopping the video is
bueno ya va parando el vídeo lo va
commenting on it
comentando
what is a reaction
lo que es una reacción
of course it's going to appear in these
por supuesto va a aparecer en estas
people so they think about the
personas así que piensan en los
paranormal
paranormales
we're going to see gray moments we're going
vamos a ver momentos grises ya nos vamos
to another one
a otro
already has a video
ya tiene un vídeo
but not even to sing
pero ni a cantar
first
primero
no ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha I
no
see that Lolita or Nolito is good or from the
eso lo veo lolita o nolito sirve o del
video God
vídeo dios
to
para
exhibit it's not that it doesn't even say what
exhibir a no es que no dice ni lo que
the song says life
dice la canción vida
attentive I don't
atentos
want the brute please Lolito
no quiero el bruto porfavor lolito
send us the brute the brute had what was his
mándanos el bruto el bruto tuvo como se
name frenan flow send us the
llamaba frenan flow que nos mande el
brute please I want to see this video the
bruto por favor quiero ver este vídeo el
brute the whole piece of the little bear is that it does
bruto el trozo del osito entero es que
n't even say what the song of
no dice ni lo de la canción de
huascachaca girl says sari
huascachaca nena dice sari voz de
hardware voice chiriboga guard nor goat
hardware chiriboga guardia ni chivo
[Laughter]
[Risas]
good  how good the lolito uncle is the
de bueno qué bueno el lolito tío es el
best
mejor
end
fin
[Laughs]
[Risas]
today
hoy
activity
actividad
nn
nn
danielle grace
danielle gracia
favorite
favorito
sometimes a normal reaction
a veces una reacción normal
returning to the subject
volviendo al tema
with a normal reaction like mine I
con una reacción normal como la mía
don't know I don't know if it says another there will be some
no sé no sé si pone otra habrán algunas
better many others worse you may
mejores muchos otros peores te puede
like it more or you may not like it but
gustar más o no te puede gustar pero
I are mostly it is valid there are
yo son en su mayoría es válido hay
some that are very light
algunas que son muy light
but it is what there is I don't know I do not
pero es que lo que hay yo que no sé no
understand does not understand the game the desire to
entiendo no entiende el juego el ansia
destroy the juke and that damaged accept
por destruir el juke y que dañó aceptar
and yuki for gave in the community to the
y yuki por dio en la comunidad a la
attention and what was suspicious is that they
atención y lo que era sospechoso es que
are you that he was trying to hide
están you que estaba intentado ocultar
all this information so that it would not be
todo esta información para que no se
known for everyone the two children who
supiera para todos los dos hijos que
come from the failed turbo plan
vienen del fracasado turbo plan le
informed him that they are on the channel to be
informó que estén en el canal de estar
yuki here we only solved and reactions
yuki aquí sólo resolvimos y reacciones
for those who cannot see it on their
para los que no pueden verlo en su
street and we do not monetize any of the
street y no monetizamos ninguno de los
videos that we upload and we give credit to
vídeos que subimos y damos el crédito de
the original videos the description of
los vídeos originales la descripción de
each video or whatever there is this channel was
cada vídeo o lo que hay este canal era
really his he even deleted you do so
suyo realmente incluso borraba les haces
much of his channel from his community
tanto de su canal de su comunidad
even messages from albums that are
incluso mensajes de discos que están
completely deleted because he wanted to
completamente eliminados porque quería
hide it but that we have obtained
ocultarlo pero que los hemos conseguido
collect and we have screenshots even though they have already been
recopilar y tenemos capturas aunque ya
deleted admitting that the channel was
se hayan borrado admitiendo que el canal
indeed hers thanks to my videos
pues sí era suyo gracias a mis vídeos
she did an interview with him her
ella hizo una entrevista con él su
brother in which speaking with him he
hermano en el que hablando con él
admitted on his own word that the
admitió de su propia palabra que el
boom and armie channel is hers I created a
canal boom y armie si es suyo yo creé un
jagger
jagger
because my community
porque mi comunidad
asked me to upload
me pedía que lo que se subiera
my reactions to the things I made
mis reacciones de las cosas que hacía
videos and these the channel is hers
vídeos y éstas el canal es suyo
in fact my main thing that I did not
de hecho mi principal cosa que yo no
want to do my main face
quería hacer mi cara principal
that I did not upload it to her main channel
que no lo subí a su canal principal
because she did not like to upload that she
porque no le gustaba subir eso sea ella
herself knows perfectly well that what she
misma sabe perfectamente que lo que
did was wrong and that is why I
hacía estaba mal y es por eso que
use this channel supposedly of
utilizo este canal supuestamente de
followers not to try to sneak out
seguidores no para intentar escabullirse
saying no well it is that this channel is
decir no bueno es que este canal es
then here star jung lied and of some
entonces aquí mintió star jung y de unos
followers and if it passes then it passes that stop it did
seguidores y si cuela pues cuela que
not pass because people do not
para pues que no coló porque la gente no
this or rather it is being here that I have
esto o sea está siendo aquí que he
created by followers when she already says that she
creado por seguidores cuando ya dice que
created it because at the beginning she says
la creado ella porque al principio dice
no it is that that channel
no es que ese canal
please could it be a gif of lolita
por favor podría ser un gif de lolita
can you make me there is here
podéis hacer me hay de está por aquí
airén I want a gif of lolita and the
airén quiero un gif de lolita y el
sound of lolita saying play and I go
sonido de lolita diciendo jugar y voy
origami wow wow and I'm going to put it at
origami wow wow y lo voy a poner a los
300 I live some of that is worth it because
300 vivo algo de eso vale porque me lo
my fans asked me to so they could see my
pedían mis fans para poder ver mis
summary videos but then however
vídeos resumidos pero luego sin embargo
a little later he admits that he created that channel
un poco después admite que ese canal lo
to advertise his
creó para darse publicidad a su canal de
twitter channel which is precisely what
twitter que es precisamente lo que
we criticized in the videos I'm not
nosotros criticábamos en los vídeos no
going to lie it's also for
voy a mentir lo para también
exposure
exposición
so
entonces
what happened here is
qué ha pasado aquí
the look and it hadn't sold there's something I do
está el look y no había vendido hay algo
n't understand why so much problem
que no entiendo por qué tanto problema
with her she doesn't just do reactions to the
con ella ella no hace solo reacciones al
show I knew her from her
show yo la conocí por sus vídeos de
dance videos on tw consensus I don't understand what's
baile en tw consenso no entiendo qué
going on with her about the
pasa con ella del hombre encogido de
shrugged man where it lines you don't get radioactive
hombros donde raya no te radiactivo
thanks for your hanger host dude he
gracias por tu su percha [__] tío nos
left us sold the church yuki dude I
ha dejado vendió la church yuki tío o
mean it turns out I believe it she who
sea resulta que se lo creo ella que ha
put in the description that you are her
puesto en la descripción que eres sus
followers and on top of that it will turn
seguidores y encima luego
out to remove recognizing that I did it
resultará quitar reconociendo que lo he
to gain more fame she
hecho para ganar más fama
left us
nos ha dejado
and we're 4 minutes into the video and there are 21
y llevamos 4 minutos de vídeo y son 21
the thing is to recognize it precisely I
la cosa reconocerlo precisamente lo
did it from a channel of some followers
hacía desde un canal de unos seguidores
because she knows perfectly well that it is not
porque sabe perfectamente que no está
right to do that and the other day well the
bien hacer eso y el otro día bueno el
other day a week or two weeks  I don't know
otro día una semana o dos semanas no sé
exactly recently Yuki showed
exactamente hace poco estar yuki mostró
her hypocrisy by not getting very angry with
su hipocresía no enfadándose mucho con
her followers because they uploaded
sus seguidores porque le subían el
content that she did, they tweeted, they didn't
contenido que ella pues hacían tweets no
upload it to YouTube channels and
lo subían pues a canales de youtube y
according to her, that's very wrong because it
según ella pues eso está muy mal porque
's stealing content and also unedited and
es robar contenido y además sin editar y
that's hers
eso pues es suyo
because it goes to my channel if they upload it I'm going to
porque va a mi canal si lo suben voy a
give them a strike I'm going to delete the
darles un strike voy a borrar les el
video and I'm going to give them a strike because
vídeo y les voy a dar un strike porque
because it's my video and they're my things or I'm
porque en mi vídeo y son mis cosas o
left here like a little unfair that
quedo aquí como que un poco injusto que
people
personas
come and put the full video
vengan pongan el vídeo completo y
edited or anything and just like that because
editado ni nada y simplemente así porque
if she already took the video it seems
si ya se lleve el vídeo me parece
quite hypocritical to me not taking into account
bastante hipócrita no teniendo en cuenta
that more than 70% of the content that you have
que más del 70% del contenido que has
uploaded to YouTube is
subido a youtube es contenido
completely stolen content that does have
completamente robado que sí que tiene
another 30% of content that is hers
otro 30% de contenido que sí que es suyo
and that are not reaction videos but we
y que no son vídeos reacciones pero es
are talking about 70
que estamos hablando de que un 70 por
percent of the content that has been uploaded to
ciento del contenido que ha subido a
YouTube is stolen so it's very
youtube es robado entonces es muy
hypocritical of you to complain and on top of that
hipócrita que tú te quejes y encima
threaten to delete their channel or
amenaces con borrarles el canal o
give your followers a strike for
meterles un strike a tus seguidores por
receive content that is also
recibir un contenido que aparte es un
content that is not you
contenido que de por sí no es tú
look god it
mira dios
doesn't come out
no sale
look
mira
well I just received a notification
bueno me acaba de llegar notificación
from the plus de plus salsa whatsapp group I
del grupo de whatsapp de plus de plus
'm going to see what's going on I understand
salsa voy a ver qué va
the truth I really understand that
entiendo la verdad yo entiendo de verdad
this is coming nothing I'm going to watch it on my
que viene eso nada voy a verlo en el
phone
móvil
with 8
con 8
thanks thanks I'm going to I'm
gracias gracias
going to tweet it
voy a voy a twittear lo
but I want a gif I
pero quiero un gif
want to convert this into a
quiero convertir esto en una
notification for my stream okay
notificación de mi stream vale
how disgusting man of truths
qué asco tío de verdades
but when reading the statement that this
pero al leer el comunicado que ha
yuc has written and communicated in the wake of
escrito estar yuc y comunicado a raíz de
the recent situations that have been
las recientes situaciones que han estado
happening and that
sucediendo y que personas
malicious people are trying to
malintencionadas están intentando
harm me with videos that are totally
hacerme daño con vídeos totalmente
meaningless I feel
carentes de sentido me veo en la
obliged to release this statement
obligación de sacar este comunicado
videos videos totally
vídeos vídeos totalmente carentes de
meaningless already navas start reading the
sentido ya navas empezar a leer el
statement it seems like she wants to
comunicado se ve como que ella quiere
ridicule not all the videos well
ridiculizar no todos los vídeos bueno
obviously she's referring to my video I do
obviamente se refiere a mi vídeo creo
n't think you have to be very smart to realize it
que no hace falta ser muy avispado para
but she's kind of
darse cuenta pero ella pues como que
trying to ridicule as if the videos
trata de ridiculizar como si los vídeos
or the video that he has made didn't make
o el vídeo que él ha hecho no tuviera
any sense as if it were I don't know how
ningún sentido como si fuera no sé como
some kind of madness and in what
una especie de locura y en lo que he
I said in my video no, it's
dicho yo en mi vídeo no que es
basically  that estar yuki steals
básicamente que estar yuki roba
content and summarizes it on her channel with her
contenido y lo resume a su canal con
whole face simply by putting her
toda la cara simplemente poniendo su
face next to it and doing nothing but be careful
cara al lado y sin hacer nada pero ojo
this is not the only one I said this is
es que esto no solo lo he dicho yo esto
not just my opinion this is what
no es sólo mi opinión esto lo opinan
many other people think even in my
muchas otras personas incluso en mi
last video I made it because
último vídeo yo lo hice a raíz de que
several strippers not like vigil the girlfriend
varias strippers no como vigil la novia
of hurón plate and there is an hour ago who is another
de hurón plate y hay horita que es otra
streamer came out to give their opinion on
streamer salieron a dar su opinión sobre
this type of streamer although they did not say
este tipo de streamer aunque no dijeron
exactly the name of star djukic
exactamente el nombre de star djukic
we know that you are referring to her
sabemos que te refieres a ella
I think that there is no other person who
yo creo que no hay otra persona que
has more reaction videos than estar
tenga más vídeos reacciones que estar
yuki I think that maybe I am wrong and
yuki creo que a lo mejor me equivoco y
less because they continue with her
menos porque se siguen con ella
you would be criticizing another person
estarías criticando a otra persona
how everything has changed
cómo ha cambiado todo
how everything has changed in a while until
cómo ha cambiado todo en un rato hasta
today eh
hoy eh
how [ __ ] up is the [ __ ] life done at the
qué jodida es la [__] vida hecho a la
same time
vez
how [ __ ] up is the [ __ ] life
qué jodida es la [__] vida
and there is another person who has many more
y hay otra persona que tiene muchas más
and I am amazed in colors but as far as I know as
y flipo en colores pero que yo sepa tan
exaggerated as estar yuki I do not know of
exagerado como estar yuki yo no conozco
any case this is not just my
ningún caso que esto no es sólo mi
opinion there are other people who also
opinión hay otras personas que también
think that doing this is having a lot of
piensan que hacer esto es de tener mucha
nerve a lot of face or very little  shameful
jeta mucha cara o muy poca vergüenza
whatever you want to call it is
como lo quieras llamar es
this
esto
because they are understanding with your video
porque están entendiendo con tu vídeo
that it is entertaining
que está entreteniendo
reaction to a car video look
reacción a un vídeo de auto mira
your eyes will not see it from here doing a
no lo verán tus ojos de aquí haciendo un
cameo of atoyac and making a little path you do
cameo de atoyac y haciendo un caminito
not see me because I am here
no me veis porque estoy aquí
hey but wait for me hey hey hey
oye pero espera para mí
sorry that it is
perdonad que sea es
this type of content does it well I am not
este tipo de contenido lo hace bueno
going to say no I do not want either I do not
no voy a decir no tampoco quiero no
want to talk but this type of things to
quiero hablar pero este tipo de cosas a
me no thanks thank you but no I do not
mí no gracias thank you pero no no me
like to react or hang on a video
gusta reaccionar ni colgarme de un vídeo
especially of the magnitude that
sobre todo de las magnitudes que tiene
Raúl has it seems even funny to me I am
raúl me parece hasta chistoso soy poco
unethical and also if the video criticism that
ético y aparte si la vídeo crítica que
I have made you was totally just
yo te he hecho fuera totalmente
stolen turbo content I raise what
me acaba de robar contenido turbo
poor people lacking
planteo menudo y pobre gente carente de
severe moderate stupidity well I do not
severo de moderada una estupidez pues no
understand what you are doing responding with this
entiendo qué hace respondiendo con este
long statement something that does not make
comunicado tan largo algo que no tiene
any sense not since I started
ningún sentido no desde que empecé a
doing streams in tweets four years ago I have
hacer streams en tweets hace cuatro años
never gotten into any type of
nunca me he metido en ningún tipo de
controversy with anyone from the dual ballet this
polémicas con nadie del ballet dual esto
well has absolutely nothing to
bueno no tiene absolutamente nada que
do not with the issue of stealing videos and with
ver no con el tema de robar vídeos y con
the issue of video reactions but
el tema de las vídeo reacciones pero
okay or whatever it seems to me  ok that in four
vale o sea me parece bien que en cuatro
years you have never messed with anyone
años nunca te hayas metido con nadie
but the fact that you have not
pero el hecho de que tú no te hayas
messed with anyone or have not gotten into
metido con nadie o no te hayas metido en
controversies these last four years does not
polémicas estos últimos cuatro años no
prevent you from making
te quita de que tú puedas cometer
mistakes or doing things that are not well
errores o hacer cosas que no están bien
seen like trying videos from other
vistas como probar vídeos de otros
youtubers I have always tried to create
youtubers he tratado de crear siempre
a healthy and beautiful community a
una comunidad sana y hermosa una
community that can be called
comunidad a la que se le puede llamar
family okay many colleagues and streamers
familia vale muchos colegas y streamers
have told me when I chat with
me lo han dicho cuando colom oro con
someone my chat goes to the other channel to
alguien mi chat va hacia el otro canal a
spread good vibes and affection it makes me very
tirar buena onda y cariño me pone muy
happy to have the community that I have anything is
feliz tener la comunidad que tengo todo
worth it but what is this statement for is
vale pero el comunicado este para qué es
to lick the left ball of your
para lamerle el huevo izquierdo a tu
community because okay we already know that your
comunidad porque vale ya sabemos que tu
community is very good but is
comunidad es muy buena pero se supone
this statement supposed to talk about
que este comunicado es para hablar de
the issue of video reactions
el tema de las vídeos reacciones
thank you very much I talk about the community
muchas gracias habló sobre la comunidad
because it is the only opinion that
porque es la única opinión que me
interests me those who know my story and
interesa los que conocen mi historia y
those who got me out of depression well I did
los que me sacaron de la depresión bueno
not know about this but I suppose it
de esto no lo sabía pero supongo que no
has nothing to do with the issue of
tiene nada que ver con el tema de las
video reactions and stolen videos you
vídeos reacciones y los vídeos robados
are not talking about that your community is
no estás hablando de que tu comunidad es
very good that on the other hand I believe it
muy buena que por otro lado me lo creo
but I do not know no  it has nothing to do with the
pero no sé no tiene nada que ver con el
topic no good and we're going to keep reading to
tema no bueno y vamos a seguir leyendo a
see what a few
ver qué dice lo que digan unos cuantos
haters say sincerely I've been going through it
haters sinceramente me lo paso por él
for a long time buying hick
desde hace mucho tiempo de compre paleto
alcohol life it doesn't matter fact I want to
alcohol vida no importa hecho quiero
see it wanting to leave the town alone
verlo querer irse solo del pueblo
to that content is not right and that's why you
a ese contenido no está bien y por eso
don't upload it to your channel but I want to see
no lo subes a tu canal pero quiero ver
the town
el pueblo
okay I'm not interested I'm
vale no me interesa
not interested it's a
no me interesa
lie you're lying you talk without
es mentira estás mintiendo de hablas sin
informing yourself be yuki has two channels
informarte estar yuki tiene dos canales
on youtube one called start yuki
en youtube uno que se llama start yuki
with a million followers and another
con un millón de seguidores y otro que
called boom and armin with three hundred
se llama boom y armin con trescientos
thousand followers in total between these two
mil seguidores en total entre estos dos
channels he has 435 videos of which
canales tiene 435 vídeos de los cuales
165 belong to star yuki and 270
165 pertenecen a star yuki y 270
belong to boom and arm and already this
pertenecen a boom y arm y ya ya este
fact should alarm some of us not
dato ya debería alarmarnos algunos no en
like that in the boom and arm channel and that it is
plan que en el canal boom y arm y que es
an eye channel of one hundred percent of the 270
un canal ojo de cien por cien de los 270
videos the 270 are unedited reaction videos of
vídeos los 270 son vídeo reacciones sin
other people's videos with their
editar de vídeos otras personas con su
face next to them without saying anything well I
cara al lado sin decir nada bueno
have to admit that
tengo que admitir que le queda muy cool
the town fashion looks very cool on turbo plant but I don't
la moda de pueblo a turbo plant pero no
understand the hate  the girl x there are
entiendo el hate a la chica x de hay
worse characters in hito they only talk about
peores personajes en hito solo hablan de
her in her town
ella en su pueblo
is that if I don't understand either look has
es que si no entiendo tampoco mira ha
done here this math of the colleague I
hecho aquí estas matemáticas del colega
don't understand either the tenant
tampoco entiendo la inquilina
well it's a little high it's a little
bueno es un poco subido es un poco
more things and even so the people
más cosas y aún así la gente
the only thing that changes things the only thing
lo único que cambia la cosa el lo único
that changes things is that it has been able to
que cambia la cosa es que se haya podido
give publicity with
dar publicidad con
with the thing of life and reactions okay
con lo de la vida y reacciones vale
for here it comes here it comes from the town
para aquí viene aquí viene del pueblo
but we have also seen that the
pero hemos visto también que los vídeos
most viewed videos staciuk and they were others therefore it has
más vistos staciuk y fueron otros por lo
also become known to
tanto se ha hecho conocida también a
many followers with other types of
muchísimos seguidores con otro tipo de
videos okay and on the other hand it is that
vídeos vale y por otra parte es que la
people at the same time do what I do every
gente la vez haga lo que haga yo cada
time I go to tweets let's see if
vez que voy a tweets vamos a ver si
now I think
ahora
the clock is going to come out the name
creo que el reloj va a salir el nombre
is you which is a while precisely
está you que es un rato precisamente
life two million let's
la vida dos millones
see well be yuki has two million
a ver pues estar yuki tiene dos millones
followers and they set the views that
de seguidores y fijaron las visitas que
each live has at the see that you
tiene cada directos a la ven que te
[ __ ]
cagas
lavín that you [ __ ] the time a lot I don't
lavín que te cagas la vez muchísimo no
know how many viewers it has but
sé cuántos espectadores tiene pero tal
maybe you see that the live video
vez que ves que el vídeo en directo
has four or five or six thousand
tiene cuatro o cinco o seis mil
viewers
espectadores
the criticisms that have been made are
las críticas que han hecho son carentes
meaningless that's why  They choose to mess
de sentido por eso eligen meterse
with me because I'm not used to being
conmigo que no estoy acostumbrada estar
in controversies and I have a
en polémicas y tengo una comunidad
quiet community but when someone who knows how to
tranquila pero cuando alguien que sabe
debate challenges them to a debate then they
debatir les reta a un debate entonces se
[ __ ] their pants and hide
cagan en los pantalones y se esconden
well I think that he clearly
bueno yo creo que esto claramente lo
says this as if to give me a zasca and not because of
dice como para meterme un zasca y no por
the Dallas debate I didn't want to
el debate de dallas tampoco quería yo
relive this whole issue because
revivir todo este tema porque ya está
everything is already resolved but no it wasn't like that no it
todo solucionado pero no no fue así no
wasn't like that this Balenciaga I was the
no fue así esto balenciaga yo fui el
first one who rejected Dallas to do a
primero que le rechaza a dallas hacer un
debate it came out I challenged him to do a
debate salió le rete a él hacer un
debate and the fdt also from the
debate y el fdt igual del sector de
carache sector so yes it was like turbo plan in the
carache tal si fue así turbo plan al
end it was done because of fighting with me
final se hizo porque de batirse conmigo
and already being here live Dallas said
y ya estando aquí en directo dallas dijo
his life and you said okay that he should
de su vida y tú dijiste que vale que
go up
subiera
but yes easy like that it was like that he was the first one who did
pero si fácil así fue así fue el primero
n't want to do it in fact Bernal from
que no quiso hacerlo de hecho bernal de
Instagram then a week later
instagram luego una semana después me
challenged me to do the debate and I didn't want to and
retó el hacer el debate y yo no quise y
well in the end a few months later we
bueno al final unos meses después lo
ended up doing the debate and well in
acabamos haciendo el debate y bueno de
fact we ended up solving the
hecho acabamos solucionando los
problems of all of these well I think
problemas de todos estos bueno pues creo
no it's not the point but well I  just in
que no no viene al cuento pero bueno yo
case I clarify on purpose the
por si acaso lo aclaro a propósito los
videos we watch is that they get
vídeos que vemos es que les entra la
anxious it serves a little bit of falling
ansiedad se sirve de un poquillo de caer
from battlefield currently I have
de battlefield actualmente tengo
authorization to watch them, I have spoken
autorización para verlos he hablado en
privately with the owner of each channel to
privado con el dueño de cada canal para
ask for their permission and some of them are
pedirles permiso y algunos de ellos son
even friends of mine and this girl already
hasta amigos míos y esta chica ya
reacted to euro's videos in play
reaccionaba a los vídeos de euro en play
I am not saying this she said this in
esto no lo digo yo esto lo dijo ella en
her brother's interview she already
la entrevista de su hermano ella ya
reacted to the videos of a play
reaccionaba a los vídeos de un play
even before opening a play
incluso antes de que abra un play
was on twitch I mean I have to
estuviera en twitch o sea me tengo que
believe that you have had the permission of aurum
creer que tú tienes el permiso de aurum
play for more than four years no
play desde hace más de cuatro años no
but now she does say it is that at the
pero ahora sí lo tiene dijo es que en el
moment that she has to remove it to everyone
momento que lo tiene que sacar a todos
well anyway a little disappointed
bueno en fin un poquito decepcionado
because he has been defending it
porque él ha estado defendiendo
and then it turns out that she herself has
y luego resulta ser que ella mismo ha
recognized
reconocido
that if the channel is hers okay that I am the
que si el canal es suyo vale que soy el
channel and that she has done it to
canal y que lo ha hecho para
advertise herself but well it will not happen there
publicitarse pero bueno no pasará
are no worse crimes but it
tampoco las hay crímenes peores pero me
has hurt me it is more it hurts a little but
ha dolido es más duele un poco pero
now she is breaking the corner with
ahora está partiendo la esquina con
these girls you know what
estas chicas sabes qué
[Music]
[Música]